



Ionut-Claudiu Leonte

O Home: Bucharest, Romania

Email: leonteionut98@yahoo.com Phone: (+40) 727304987

Website: https://leonte-portfolio.netlify.app/

Website: https://github.com/leonteionutclaudiu

(C) Whatsapp Messenger: +40727304987

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/leonte-ionut-claudiu/

Date of birth: 20/06/1998 Nationality: Romanian

ABOUT ME

In the past: I worked at CLdN Malta Ltd as an Engine Cadet with an international team. Now: I studied the "Junior Front-end Web Development" course at IT School and I Jearn

Future goal: I look forward to working as a Junior Front-end Web Developer.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[07/2022 - 01/2023]

Junior Front-end Web Developer

IT School

Address: Timisoara

Field(s) of study: Computer Software Engineering HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React.js, Git

[2017 - 2021] **Constanta Maritime University**

Faculty of Naval Electromechanics

Address: Constanta, Romania Field(s) of study: Engineering

Final grade: 9.00

[2013 - 2017] High school graduation

"Nicolae Bălcescu" National College, Brăila

Address: Brăila, Romania

Field(s) of study: Mathematics - Informatics (informatics intensive)

Final grade: 8.38

WORK EXPERIENCE

[2021 - 2022] **Engine Cadet - Ro/Ro Ships**

CLdN Malta Ltd.

- Had 3 trips contracts in 2021-2022 year.
- Assisting with any planned maintenance work.
- · Helping to operate pump and fuel systems, distribution and electrical generating equipment, air conditioning plants, refrigeration systems, and cranes and lifts.
- Stripping engines and inspecting their components.

- Tracing out (following) the paths of oil, water or steam as they travel through the ship's systems.
- Taking note of daily logs from the equipment in the engine room.
- Taking soundings (measuring how much fluid is in a tank.)
- Helping to keep watch in the engine room.
- Cleaning, painting and greasing equipment

DIGITAL SKILLS

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Bootstrap | React | Git

PROJECTS

Personal Portfolio

Link: https://github.com/leonteionutclaudiu/leonte-personal-portfolio

LeonteSocial - Social Media App in React

Link: https://github.com/leonteionutclaudiu/leontesocial

Leonte-Banking Website

Link: https://github.com/leonteionutclaudiu/leonte-banking-website

Leonte-Banking App

Link: https://github.com/leonteionutclaudiu/Leonte-Banking

Leonte-Food Website

Link: https://github.com/leonteionutclaudiu/leonte-food

COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Communication

Teamwork

Flexible Schedule

Easily Adaptable

Active-learning

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Romanian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C2 READING C2 WRITING C2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C2 SPOKEN INTERACTION C2

German

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

HOBBIES

Travelling, Sports, Cars, Music, Movies, Video Gaming

DRIVING LICENCE

Cars: B

Yes